So this pirate butler,
he killed your friend's lawyer
and he's threatening to kill your friend?
My best friend, Kaya.
He's up to something.
Who pretends to be a butler anyway?
You're not actually buying any of this,
are you?
Well, I'm telling the truth.
Klahadore is a pirate. No, sorry. Kuro.
- His name is Captain Kuro.
- Ha! Now I know you're lying.
- Captain Kuro of the Black Cat Pirates?
- Yes. Long claws, tiny glasses.
Impossible. My father,
Axe-Hand Morgan, killed him years ago.
Any Marine worth their salt knows that.
No closer to finding Straw Hat
than we were hours ago.
Straw Hat? You mean Luffy?
Wait. You know Luffy?
My other, other best friend.
He's in trouble.
- Luffy's at the place?
- Yes! Aren't you listening to me?
Someone has to stop Kuro.
I can't do it by myself.
It's okay. We're here to help.
Isn't that right?
Well, yes.
By all means.
Lead the way.
Luffy.
Luffy!
Oh, come on.
Yes.
Do you understand?
I understand, sir.
I just left Miss Kaya in her room.
What is he doing here?
What's wrong with him?
Little guy couldn't get enough
of my latest recipe.
I was chasing that perfect balance
between bitter and savory.
Just wish I could've asked him
how it tasted.
- It tasted like poison, idiot.
- Not while I'm the cook.
You're not a cook.
I'm not a maid. We're pirates.
Sell yourself short, Sham,
but leave my cooking out of...
Enough!
I can't hear myself think
over your inbred nonsense!
Now, how much of the soup did he eat?
Uh...
All of it.
How fortuitous.
Go ahead and toss him in the well
with the green-haired oaf.
Aye aye, Captain.
And don't you dare track in mud
all over my floors again.
Says the maid.
Who'd ring the bell at this hour?
Just stay put.
Understood?
Let's not allow the night
to get the better of us.
Marines?
Whatever could be the matter
at this time of night?
Sorry to bother you at such a late hour,
but we heard reports
of pirates in the area.
What? What are you talking about?
He is the pirate!
He murdered Merry!
Arrest him. What are you waiting for?
Oh dear.
I'm so sorry
if Usopp here has wasted your time.
You see, he's not well.
The entire village
has tried their utmost to help, but
the poor boy has been this way
ever since he was a child.
One lie bigger than the next.
He was never quite the same
after his mother's passing.
Leave my mother out of this.
His gloves! Check his gloves for blades.
Do you mind if we have a look?
Just to be certain.
Well...
I'm not sure where he gets these ideas.
A butler's gloves. Such an imagination.
I guess some fruit gets so bruised,
it can't help
but to be rotten at the core.
But, uh, I know what I saw.
All right. That's enough.
I thought we had a job to do.
We're looking for a fugitive.
Goes by the name of Luffy.
Luffy?
Luffy, why, yes, I do know that name.
Belongs to one of the lowly criminals
Usopp has introduced
to the lady of the house.
Horrible bunch. Drank the place dry.
I have one of the staff members
keeping an eye on him now.
Buchi, the Marines are here.
They've come to collect
the drunken Straw Hat Pirate.
Bring him to the front of the house
at once.
Marines.
- What are we gonna do?
- Nothing.
But what if the Straw Hat talks?
He drank enough of that soup
to kill a sea beast.
Stick to the captain's plan.
Come on, sweetheart.
You've got it all wrong.
Luffy is a pirate, sure,
but not like Kuro.
It's... it's confusing, but please.
Kaya. Kaya's in danger!
Sorry, Usopp. You don't have any proof.
There's nothing I can do.
What's wrong with him?
Insatiable appetite, I suppose.
Too much food, too much liquor.
But for a pirate, nothing is ever enough.
Good thing we have Marines like yourselves
to keep the East Blue safe.
Now, if that is all,
I really must return to my duties.
Wait. I just have a few more questions.
Of course.
- What was that?
- Old houses.
You know, they're just like us.
The older they get, the more they creak.
You sure?
It sounded like...
I shall stick to my expertise
and leave you to yours.
You do have your fugitive in hand
after all.
- He's lying. Everything he says...
- That's enough out of you.
Help! Please!
Pirates! Somebody, help!
Please, pirates! Someone, help, please!
Can't reason with madness.
Now, I really must return to my duties.
On behalf of the Marines, we thank...
Again!
Ah.
Fight!
Again!
Next!
You're dropping your elbow.
Just some friendly advice.
We're not friends, Kuina.
And I don't need advice from you.
Your movements say otherwise.
Have you learned anything
during your time here?
Don't mock me!
I'm the best fighter here other than you.
And one day, I'm gonna surpass you.
Then I'm gonna be
the world's greatest swordsman.
Maybe one day.
But not today.
I know why I can't beat you.
It's these bamboo swords.
Let's fight with real blades
to see who's best.
Fine.
Katanas it is.
But if you want to beat me,
you'd better be ready to kill me.
Okay. Plan B.
Kaya!
Kaya, hurry up! Let me in!
Open the window!
- Usopp?
- Yeah, hurry up.
Hurry up. Come on.
Kaya.
There's pirates in the house.
I know. You invited them.
No, not those pirates. The other pirates.
You're in danger.
- Usopp, you're not making any sense.
- Please, Kaya, we gotta get out of here.
I'm not going anywhere.
It's the middle of the night.
How about I ring for Klahadore?
We can have...
No, don't call Klahadore!
He's the one trying to hurt you.
He killed Merry.
Merry?
He was here only a few hours ago.
Yeah. Now he's dead.
Klahadore isn't a butler.
He's...
he's a vicious pirate.
Usopp, you're scaring me.
Klahadore gave up his life to care for me.
Why would he want to hurt me? Hurt Merry?
I... I don't know.
Maybe he wants your money.
Usopp.
Kaya,
please, just believe me.
You always believe me.
I believed your stories
because they were fun. This one isn't.
This isn't a story.
It's the truth. You gotta listen!
I don't think you know
what the truth is anymore.
I think you should go, Usopp.
- Kaya...
- Please.
Just go.
No.
I'm done running.
I'm not leaving your side.
Not until I know you're safe.
Sham!
What the hell happened?
The orange-haired girl.
She was hiding.
She overheard everything.
And you let her get away?
She came out of nowhere.
The time for waiting is over.
Kaya is of age.
And we can finally put this farce to bed.
So we kill her now?
Yes, Buchi.
No more hiding who we are.
And to be absolutely certain
we're not interrupted,
lock the house down.
Yes, Captain.
What's that?
The security shutters.
My parents built them
to keep the pirates out.
But now they're keeping the pirates in...
with us.
Thank God you're still alive.
Why wouldn't we be alive?
Ah!
Poison?
What are you talking about?
I overheard them in the kitchen.
It's been going on for years.
- Did Usopp put you up to this?
- I didn't even know.
I gave you that tea.
Think about it, Kaya.
When did you start getting sick?
Was it around the time
Kuro started working here?
Listen to me.
If we stay here, we die.
We have to leave now.
Kaya.
Oh, Miss Kaya.
Kaya!
We're all alone now.
Why,
parents are gone.
Your friends are all gone.
Even Usopp is gone.
It's just you and me, Miss Kaya.
It's time
to wake up!
Where are we going?
We gotta get out of the house.
Another crank
can open the shutters.
It's in my parents' bedroom
in the east wing.
Are you sure?
Maybe there's another way.
This is the only option. We have to go...
There you are, Miss Kaya.
It's your birthday.
It's time to celebrate!
Run!
Ready to learn your lesson?
Not in this lifetime. Let's end this.
Two swords not enough?
Maybe you should've brought more.
You're dropping your elbow again.
Shut up and fight!
I can't beat you.
Just kill me.
I don't deserve to wield a sword.
Don't be an idiot.
You've always had raw skill.
And you'll only get better.
You'll surpass me
in size, strength, and speed.
Eventually,
you'll surpass me in everything.
That's dumb.
No, that's nature.
I'm small now.
And fast. But soon,
all the boys will get taller and stronger.
Their arms will be longer than mine.
Who cares about that kind of stuff?
Don't you get it?
Girls can beat boys,
but no woman can beat a man.
Don't say that.
Don't make excuses.
You're my goal.
If you just give up,
what has all our training been for?
Let's fight every day.
We'll keep getting better and stronger
until one of us becomes the greatest.
You'd do that for me?
I, Roronoa Zoro,
vow to fight, train,
and kick your butt every single day.
Then I, Shimotsuki Kuina,
vow to fight, train,
and kick your butt every single day.
If we keep that vow, one of us will become
the world's greatest swordsman...
Or woman.
...to ever live.
I don't know.
Something feels really off about this.
You know, you're the only person I know
who'd actually feel bad
about capturing the fugitive
you're supposed to capture.
I know that Usopp guy might be full of it,
but that butler gives me the creeps.
Sure, take the side of the pirates.
I'm sure Garp would love that too.
It's not my fault I'm doing a good job,
and the Vice-Admiral sees it.
The only reason you're here is
'cause you're friends with that Straw Hat.
Garp doesn't believe in you.
He's using you.
No, he's not.
You're just jealous.
Doesn't make me wrong.
Meat.
What was that, Straw Hat?
You got something to say?
Oh.
Okay.
Big, creepy room. No problem.
It was a spider.
We treated him like family.
How did I not see it?
How did I not see him?
It's not your fault.
He took advantage of you.
Now, I need you to be strong
so we can get out of here.
What would they think of me?
- They'd be so disappointed.
- No.
No, they'd want you to survive,
and that is exactly
what we are going to do.
Pull.
Sensei.
I was just waiting for Kuina.
Do you know where she is?
Kuina is...
There was an accident.
She's...
She's gone.
But...
she can't be.
We made a promise.
Sensei, please give me the honor
of allowing me to carry Kuina's sword.
The Wado Ichimonji is a rare blade.
Why should I allow you to carry it?
Because Kuina and I made a promise
that one of us would become the world's
greatest swordsman to ever live.
Then it's up to you
to fulfill that promise.
For you
and for her.
Koby.
I gotta go back.
The butler.
He's gonna kill Kaya,
and then he's gonna go after my crew.
I'm under direct orders to bring you in.
You said you wanted
to help innocent people.
Kaya's innocent.
You know what? Screw this.
Helmeppo, don't!
Father always said, "Dead pirate
weighs the same as a live one."
- Garp gave us strict orders.
- He gave you strict orders.
Start walking, pirate,
or die.
Hey, haircut.
Zoro!
- How'd you know where to find me?
- I didn't.
Thought I was headed to the house.
Hold it right there!
By order of the Marines,
I'm placing you under arrest.
Koby...
I know you've got a job to do...
but I'm gonna go back and help my friends.
So don't try to stop me.
God, this thing needs some oil.
No, it just needs a little elbow grease.
Kaya.
Oh, Miss Kaya.
Sounds like we have
a bigger rat problem than I thought.
Maybe we need a cat in the house.
Now, now, Kaya,
I know you're in here.
Come out. There's no point
in hiding who we are anymore.
Isn't it exhausting putting on airs,
pretending we're better than we are?!
You've had every opportunity
this world has to offer.
What have you done with your life?
Nothing. Absolutely nothing!
You are a pathetic,
spoiled, sniveling little brat!
Oh, come now, Kaya.
Let's not make this
more difficult than it need be, hmm?
Just consider this payback
for all those years
spent listening to your incessant whining.
"Klahadore,
the soup's too hot."
"Bring my blanky, Klahadore."
"Make my tea. Brush my hair."
"Oh, Klahadore..."
"I miss my mommy and my daddy."
When all I wanted to do
was rip your tongue out!
Let's split up.
Where to look next?
Well, you always were Daddy's little girl,
even if he didn't have
enough time for you, hmm?
Don't.
I'm stronger than you think.
Too easy.
I thought we took out the trash.
Maybe this time, we keep his swords.
Ya!
Goodbye, Miss Kaya.
Ah.
These are my friends.
You don't get to mess with them.
You are annoyingly resilient.
Well,
I am made of rubber.
Ah!
Did you really think
you could get the best of me?
I'm Kuro of the Thousand Plans.
Usopp.
Usopp. Usopp.
Then come out and fight me.
No, you poor, poor sap.
So you think you want to be a pirate?
I am a pirate.
And how long have you been on the seas?
A week? A month?
I was a captain for years,
and I never failed in a raid.
Not once.
And what did I get in return?
A life of worry
and a target on my back
as wide as the East Blue.
Is that what you want?
A lifetime of always
looking over your shoulder.
You'll never get
a peaceful night's rest
because someone's always waiting
to slit your throat.
Pirates, Marines.
Why, even your own crew.
Not my crew.
We've got each other's backs.
Always.
Ay!
Until the day they don't.
I've killed more crewmates
than I care to remember.
They're expendable.
Every single one of them.
Sham!
Being a pirate is not about
raiding villages or perfect plans.
It's about adventure.
And freedom.
Freedom?
There's no such thing
with a bounty on your head.
You gave up on your dream.
No one who does that
can ever call themselves a pirate.
Looks like you're the one giving up now.
No.
I'm done talking.
Now I'm listening.
Ah!
You didn't plan for that, did ya?
Sham!
Gum Gum...
Bell!
Whoo!
I'm sorry about the mess.
You probably need some new staff.
I think I'm done with staff for a bit.
- Too bad we can't collect their bounty.
- No. No.
The Marines already know where we are.
We have to get out of here.
Where are we gonna go?
We don't even have a ship.
Yes,
you do.
Wow.
That looks just like your lawyer friend.
Merry ran the shipyard
after my parents passed.
He was their dearest colleague.
My oldest companion.
Then his memory will live on.
I hereby name this ship
the Going Merry!
It's yours now.
- Your new home.
- Thank you, Kaya.
Whoo!
Yeah! We did it!
Yeah!
Usopp!
What are you waiting for? Get your stuff.
What stuff?
You're coming with us. Right?
What?
Uh... uh...
No. I... I couldn't.
Just come on already.
I'm gonna need a great sharp shooter.
Just like Yasopp.
And I saw what you did back there.
Sticking up for your friends.
That's exactly the kind of guy
I need on my crew.
But...
I couldn't leave Syrup Village.
What... what about Kaya?
She needs me to take care of her.
Usopp,
you've been a great friend,
but I think it's time
I start taking care of myself.
But I said I'd never leave you.
And don't you need help with the shipyard?
The shipyard was my parents' dream.
I think I might do something different.
Like study to become a doctor.
So... I guess
this is goodbye.
I'll see you again someday.
And when I do,
I expect to hear all about
the real adventures of Captain Usopp.
They... they do know I'm the captain, right?
Let them have this one.
Hello.
Mmm.
Yahoo!
Yeah!
Oh.
I told you it would work out.
Yeah, well, don't get used to it.
Get used to what?
Being right.
I failed my first mission.
I failed to capture the target.
I didn't get Luffy.
It was just like you said.
I overthought it.
Don't be too hard on yourself.
You did exactly
what you were supposed to do.
Sir, I don't understand.
The real lesson here...
always have a back-up plan.
You flushed them out, son.
Sail ho!
Two points aft the starboard beam!
Mission accomplished.
Guys! Check it out.
Using my unparalleled artistic talent,
I made us a new Jolly Roger for the ship.
Ta-da!
I know. I know. My flair for design
often leaves people speechless.
- I already drew our flag.
- Okay, but this one is so much better.
Neither of the flags
are gonna scare anyone away.
Okay, but the Jolly Roger
is supposed to reflect the captain.
I am the captain.
- We are the Straw Hat crew.
- They call me Captain Usopp.
I am the captain.
Me, captain. Captain, me.
The captain is the one
that gets the ship
and knows the most about the ship.
I am...
Okay.
You see?
This is what it's all about.
From now on,
it's all gonna be smooth sailing.
What was that?
You had to open your mouth.
Marines! We're under attack!
Let's put one off their stern rail.
Grandpa?