But you said five degrees starboard.
Yeah, it's the other starboard,
Captain Shit-tastic.
- Thought clowns were supposed to be funny.
- What was that?
Why don't you say it to my face?
Hey! Morning, champ.
I know Luffy made a deal with you
to find Arlong, clown,
but if this is another trick...
What are you gonna do? Bleed on me?
Whoa! Whoa! Wait.
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa! What?
Because I said bleed on me?
You can bleed on me if you want.
I mean, a deal's a deal, all right?
You want your map back. I want my body.
How do we know
you're not leading us to a trap?
Zoro, buddy!
Honor amongst pirates. Right?
Come on. How about I sing
a nice sea shanty to pass the time.
♪ Oh, there once was a girl
With tangerine hair ♪
♪ Stole my map
And left me stranded somewhere ♪
♪ Truly a crafty and crooked young lass ♪
♪ But you can't deny
She had a spectacular... ♪
Ow! God, right on my nose!
Does it always take this long?
We've only been here two minutes.
Be patient.
Some days, they bite
as soon as you drop the line,
and some days, it takes hours.
And then there are days
when you don't catch anything at all.
But we're not talking
about fishing, are we?
I just want to know if Nami's okay.
A beautiful, talented woman
does not choose to ally herself
with a pirate like Arlong.
- Nami clearly needs to be rescued.
- Her tattoo says different.
Well, tattoos don't tell the whole story.
And like any woman, she's a mystery.
- Nami made her choice.
- You don't know why.
Only thing I want to hear from you
are dinner specials. You don't know Nami.
- Sounds like you don't know her either.
- I'm sure Nami has her reasons.
Whatever choice she makes...
I just need to hear it for myself.
Land ho!
- I'm gonna get you!
- No, you're not!
- I'm faster than you.
- You wish.
Snap.
Nami, it's your turn.
Nami.
Your bet.
Five hundred.
Any day now.
I'm thinking.
Oh, what's the matter?
Can't count any higher than five?
All in.
Oh!
Straight.
Ten high.
Queens full.
Ooh!
You're a liar,
and you're a cheat.
You know we don't lie about money
on this crew.
All right, game's over.
Nami, Arlong wants a word.
Sorry, boys.
I'll be back
for the rest of your Berry later.
Girls, wash up for dinner.
They had day-old biscuits
in the bakery today.
Half price, but they taste just the same.
- What's that?
- Nothing.
Where did you get this?
Where did you get the book, Nami?
I took it from the bookstore.
Why would you do that?
Because I wanted it.
You're gonna
have to do better than that.
Okay, I didn't have any money.
What? It's not like I hurt anybody.
You hurt the people you stole from.
- And yourself.
- No, they don't know what it's like.
I hate eating tangerines every day.
I hate wearing Nojiko's hand-me-downs.
I hate being poor!
We may not have much, but we have a roof
over our heads and we love each other.
- That's what makes us a family.
- No! We're not a real family.
Nojiko's not my sister.
And you're not even my mom!
I kept a plate on the stove for you.
I'm not hungry.
The day I found you and Nojiko,
my unit had been dispatched to engage
a band of pirates in the Oykot Kingdom.
But we got separated.
By the end of it, I was wounded, starving.
I thought I was gonna die.
When I saw you...
I knew I had to live.
I had to live so I could take care of you.
How did you know?
I just knew.
It was the right thing to do.
I know you'll do the right thing too.
There's a lot of memories in this room.
But you...
you should be proud.
What do I have to be proud of?
Oh, you sell yourself too short, Nami.
Thanks to you, we know every Marine base
and pirate stronghold
from here to the Goa Kingdom.
- But none of it's mine.
- True.
But you're still
a valued member of this crew, Nami.
Yeah, we make a great team.
You were gone so long, part of me
thought you might not be coming back.
Of course I came back.
We have a deal, don't we?
Yeah. I'm a fishman of my word.
Mmm.
Good girl.
Soon, fishmen will rule the East Blue.
And then on to the Grand Line
and every other sea after that.
I think the Marines might have
something to say about that.
Marines can be bought and sold.
And once they've outlived
their usefulness, crushed.
You think killing humans
will solve all your problems.
Not all.
You see, when an animal grows too wild,
it must be brought to heel.
Don't worry.
I won't forget all your hard work.
You'll have a special place in my empire.
I'd better.
Oh, Nami.
How I've missed you.
But you know, I have another job for you
in the meantime.
One of the villages
is late with their tribute payment.
Which one?
Coco Village.
I'm not exactly welcome there.
Can't you send Kuroobi or Chu?
No. This job requires a human touch.
Dining room is closed for renovations.
We need to speak to the owner.
I'm afraid the chef is busy with...
My apologies. Of course.
He'll be right with you.
- It's a nice place.
- Yeah.
My dad used to eat here all the time.
Not that he ever took me, but...
Marines, and a Vice-Admiral at that.
A little late to the party, aren't we?
I always wondered what happened
to the infamous Red Leg Zeff.
- Sir, do you know this man?
- Only by reputation.
Captain of the Cook Pirates.
Yeah, well, those days are far behind me.
I'm retired. I'm a chef now.
And the only thing under my command
is this restaurant.
We're not here for you, Red Leg.
We need some information about
a young pirate who was here recently.
Name of Luffy.
- I can't help you.
- Can't? Or won't?
These days, I'm lucky
if I remember my regulars.
Oh, you'll remember this one. Straw hat.
Always running his big mouth.
No, I'm drawing a blank.
But how about a meal on the house?
I got a dozen T-bone steaks
and a busted cooler.
It'd be such a shame to let
all that delicious marbling go to waste.
We're not here for a meal. We're here...
That steak...
Medium rare?
More rare than medium.
Never seen that before.
What could have done this?
Maybe I should head back,
make sure the Merry's secure.
Arlong did this.
Hey, shit-hat! I think we
can all agree that Arlong's a bad fish.
But why don't we quit lollygagging
and get my body back?
Pipe down in there.
Or what?
You gonna whip me up a soufflé?
- How about you take him for a while?
- Ooh, new guy carries the clown head.
Everyone! Please!
Please, everyone.
We don't have much time,
and we're short again this month.
Is it enough?
- Do we have time to get some more?
- No.
You don't.
It's Nami.
You've got a lot of nerve
showing your face here.
Got something for me?
You got something for me?
I'm sorry I took the map book.
- And you promise to never steal again?
- I promise.
- Your fingers crossed behind your back?
- Maybe.
You're not a bad kid, Nami.
You just did a bad thing.
Next time, come to me first.
Maybe we can have you
do some odd jobs around town.
- Thank you, Mr. Genzo.
- You did the right thing.
Help! Ah! Help! Everyone!
Pirates! They're attacking the village!
- What's going on?
- Help! Everyone, pirates!
There's pirates!
Citizens of Coco Village!
This town belongs to me!
Run!
You're short.
Nami, please. This is all we have.
- Arlong has bled us dry.
- Then find more blood.
Luffy?
- What are you doing here?
- I could ask you the same thing.
- This is where I belong.
- I don't believe that.
- This is not you.
- No. This isn't the me you want me to be.
Nami...
if you need our help...
No, I don't need any of you.
Arlong wanted the map,
and I conned you into getting it for me.
And you bought it.
I was never part of your stupid crew.
You don't mean that.
Take the rest of these clowns
and sail away from here.
I never want to see you again.
Okay, that went about as bad as it could.
So back to the boat
before the fishmen find us?
- Sail the hell out of here? Okay.
- There's something else going on here.
She was very clear she wants us to leave.
You don't know women.
They never say what they mean.
- Tell me again why the cook gets a say.
- Don't you guys get it? She's one of them.
She's a bad guy.
The villagers are terrified of her.
Not all of them.
Hey!
Scar guy.
Who was that lady?
You know,
the one with the cool hair?
Who wants to know?
I'm Monkey D. Luffy.
- I'm a pirate...
- Hunter.
Pirate hunter.
- We're here to collect Arlong's bounty.
- You?
I've seen men twice your size
and with twice your number
go into Arlong Park.
None of them ever came back.
- We just want to talk to her.
- Trust me, you don't.
But if it'll get you out of my town,
try the house down that road,
on the edge of the tangerine grove.
I think I got more of a boat body
than a long-journey-on-foot kind of body.
Anybody else missing the ocean?
No? Okay.
I could go bring the boat around
if we don't want to walk all the way back.
- Whoa!
- Turn around and leave. Now.
That's what I've been saying.
Hey, I saw you earlier.
I think maybe you and I have
something in common.
I've got the gun,
and you're standing in front of it.
- What could we possibly have in common?
- Let's start with Nami.
- Seems you know her very well.
- She's a thief with no conscience.
And when there's no more left to take,
she leaves and doesn't turn back.
- Now get off my property.
- Nami's part of our crew.
She's our friend.
My sister doesn't have any friends.
- The sooner you realize that, the better.
- Sisters. That makes sense.
- Both as beautiful as each other.
- Give it up.
I can tell
she really did a number on you guys.
You're not special,
and I can't help you.
- How about a meal?
- What?
An exchange of sorts
for your valuable time and information.
- You cook?
- He's a waiter.
Best cook in the East Blue.
You never tasted anything better
in your life. Usopp's word!
Ain't got much to cook with.
You'd be surprised how much I can make
with very few ingredients.
What do you say?
We have a little dinner,
a little conversation.
Fine.
But there'd better be dessert.
Mmm.
This is nothing.
You should see him at a curry house.
A fair bit better
than Marine rations, huh?
I didn't know you had the pleasure
of dining on a Marine vessel.
Only in the brig.
Where is he, Zeff? I know Luffy was here.
This is a rare vintage from Micqueot.
I've been saving it for something special.
It's been a while since I've run into
anyone from the old days,
even if we did find ourselves
on opposite sides of a cannon.
Finally got yourself
on the right side of the law.
The law had nothing to do with it.
It was time to stop.
I took my choice.
There's a new generation,
and they're coming up.
It's their time now.
Like hell it is.
Bunch of impulsive children.
Perfectly aged and ready to be enjoyed.
You leave it too long,
it'll go bad.
Or you could just serve whiskey.
Yeah!
Come on!
Arlong, we need to talk
about Coco Village.
We can talk tomorrow.
Coco Village will still be there,
provided they paid the tribute in full.
That's what we need to talk about.
That and the terms of our deal.
Always so serious, Nami.
Have a drink. Relax.
Captain Nezumi. What a pleasant surprise.
Always good to catch up, Arlong.
Although, I hear troubling news from Gosa.
Seems they've recently
been raided by pirates.
So terrible.
There are other reports as well
about fishmen stirring things up
around the Conomi Islands.
I have additional concerns.
How many?
- About twice as many as that.
- That's double our usual arrangement.
Times are changing.
It's getting harder than ever
to cover up your tracks.
Nami.
This is a party.
Let's go upstairs to discuss our business.
Nami, join us.
Dinner's served.
Mmm.
Told you.
You know, this is the best thing
I've eaten in my entire life.
Listen. There's plenty more
where that came from, but...
first, we really need to know about Nami.
The truth is...
- What's going on?
- Get in. Get in. Close the door.
Mom!
Get in.
- Mom, please.
- Stay put.
And no matter what you hear,
do not come out.
Mom!
Who's there?
Is that any way to treat a guest?
Tribute is 100,000 Berry per adult.
Go fetch it.
Take it. It's all I got.
Good.
Three plates on the table.
How many people live here?
Only one.
No record of any family.
How many people live here?
How many?
- I have two daughters.
- You'll have to pay for them.
- Fifty thousand Berry each.
- I gave you everything I have.
Too bad for you. It ain't enough.
Don't you hurt her!
- Mom.
- Oh, it's a family reunion.
The little humans, so precious.
Precious.
The money, will you take it as tribute
for my daughters?
No, Mom, you can't!
You understand what you're saying?
- I do.
- No, Mom!
Why didn't you just lie?
You didn't have to tell him about us.
Because you are my daughters,
and I would never deny that.
You deserve to live full and happy lives.
I'm sorry I couldn't do more for you.
Buy you nice things
or cook you nice meals.
I'm sorry I wasn't a very good mother.
No. No, don't say that.
Mom, no.
Mom, no! No! No! No!
Nami, Nojiko,
I love you, girls.
Wait. Nami's working for the pirate
that killed your mother?
She was just a kid.
She's not anymore.
She made her choice.
I'm tired of hearing about Nami
from other people.
She told you to leave, Luffy.
So did you.
How do you know
she's not one of Arlong's crew?
Same way I knew you weren't gonna kill me
when I cut you down from that cross.
Same way I knew about Usopp
and Sanji.
Yeah, I don't know about that waiter.
I know Nami's good.
She needs to know it too.
Tell me, Captain.
What's a fair price for your discretion?
Ten thousand Berry?
Twenty thousand?
I thought we had a fair deal.
It's not easy
keeping Marine patrols out of the area.
And with your increase in activity,
it'd be a shame if word of this
got back to Marine headquarters.
Hmm.
I guess it's just the price
of doing business.
You're a lot smarter than people
give you credit for.
Because I'm a fishman?
That's not what I...
Does it surprise you
that I have intelligence?
Ambition?
Usage beyond manual labor for humans?
Not at all. I've personally
never felt any ill will toward your kind.
And yet the leaders of the organization
you so proudly represent
saw fit to disparage
and enslave my people.
- Slavery has been abolished.
- But your prejudice remains.
Fishmen have all the same rights
as humans.
Do we?
The World Government has worked very hard
to foster better relations
between our people to keep the peace.
A fishman
is one of the Warlords of the Sea.
Jimbei is a fool!
A government dog to an inferior master.
I serve no man.
Perhaps I was a bit hasty.
I can accept the terms of our usual deal.
Yes.
You're smarter than people
give you credit for.
- And what about our deal, Arlong?
- What about it?
I have the money.
A hundred million Berry?
Nami... have you been holding out on me?
I stole that money fair and square.
Now are you ready to honor our agreement?
Bring the money to me by sunrise,
and I will consider the matter closed.
- Kuroobi.
- Mmm.
Bring Nezumi back in here.
- Go.
- Aye.
Maybe there's a way for the rat
to earn some extra Berry after all.
- Two Mistral Shooters, good man.
- Coming right up.
- What are you doing?
- Buying you a drink.
- You're welcome.
- We can't. We're on duty.
Oh, come on.
Might as well enjoy this wild goose chase.
Not much of a drinker, are you?
I still don't know why Garp has such
a bug up his arse about this Straw Hat.
- Two more.
- Aren't you full of surprises?
Is this really
what we're supposed to be doing?
What are you talking about?
Maybe the Straw Hat Pirates
aren't the villains
the Marines are making them out to be.
Thought it'd take a lot more liquor
to bring out your mutinous side.
It just seems like
if we keep making the same mistakes,
nothing's ever gonna change.
All right, out with it.
You know something.
Garp is Luffy's grandfather.
Of all the things I thought you were going
to say, that wasn't even on the list.
I should've known
from the way they both love meat.
You can't tell anyone.
It makes sense.
Why else would a vice-admiral be going
after some rubber kid playing pirate?
He's not playing.
Say what you want about Luffy,
but he's the real deal.
It doesn't matter. Not to a man like Garp.
You color outside the lines,
you get your arm chopped off.
- What?
- Seems like you can relate.
Must've been hard growing up
with a dad like...
I am nothing like that Straw Hat!
Fellow with a straw hat
came through here the other day.
Do you know where he was heading?
I might.
What's it worth to you?
And then the creature turns towards me,
flaring its tusks.
The last of the wild boars of Jaya.
Two days.
Two days, I wrestled that crazed hog
until finally I prevailed.
And I cooked it over an open flame,
and I ate it with my bare hands.
Just fire and flesh.
- And how did it taste?
- Oh.
That meat, whoa.
It was so tender,
it near melted off the bone.
It was the best meal I've ever had.
The longer they elude you,
the more satisfying the catch.
You know,
you're not tricking me
with your delicious stories.
I'm not hunting a boar.
The last thing I want to do is... put myself
in the middle of a family dispute.
The kid's special.
Reminds me of another pirate we knew
back in our glory days.
Don't say it.
It's not gonna make it less true.
The kid reminds me of Gold Roger.
And look what happened to him.
Executed.
Skewered by Marine polearms.
I don't want my...
I don't want the boy
to suffer the same fate.
He stood up for Baratie
when we were attacked.
I might be out of the game,
but I still live by the code.
Sir?
Thank you for the meal.
Have the navigator
set a course immediately
for the Conomi Islands.
- Aye, sir.
- Garp.
You have to know
when it's time to let them go.
Change is coming
whether you want it or not.
It's their turn now.
Hmm.
We'll see about that.
Tick, tick, tick, tick, tick,
tick, tick, tick, tick, tick, tick,
boom!
Yeah, I'm gonna go get some air.
Can you just be quiet?
Aw, come on. Where's the fun in that?
Do you really think your little toys
can get through the skin of a fishman?
- These are smoke bombs.
- Smoke?
That's rich.
Makes me think of how long it's been
since I've had any smoked fish.
Maybe if you guys had some extra?
Please?
Ah, screw you guys!
Arlong's gonna bite
the shit out of you anyway.
You know you don't stand a chance
against him and his army.
And you dumb pieces of garbage,
you ain't gonna do anything
against that stupid...
New guy shuts up the clown head.
How dare you?
It's not enough that you're working
for our mother's killer,
but now you're desecrating her grave too?
Nojiko. Nojiko, wait!
It's not what you think.
You have no idea what I think.
Ah!
What's this?
Is this the money that you stole?
And you're hiding it
next to our mother's body?
- Nami, what kind of monster are you?
- You don't understand.
Then make me understand.
I need to speak with you.
- And who are you?
- My name is Nami. You killed my mother.
Nami.
Oh, right, I did. The ex-Marine.
She was brave. I'll give her that.
Let me guess.
You've come to even the score.
You want to kill me, little girl?
No.
I want to join your crew.
That is rich.
But why would I ever let a human
onto my crew?
Because I have something you want.
You drew this?
This is good.
Very good.
Maybe the best I've seen in the East Blue,
fishman or human.
So let me join your crew,
and I'll help you.
Help me?
I killed your mother,
and now you want to come work for me?
Hmm.
Why would you do that?
Because you have something I want.
I told Arlong
I'd work for him on one condition.
That he let me buy back Coco Village.
And he said he would
for a hundred million Berry.
A hundred million?
- That would take a lifetime.
- I have the money.
All of it.
And now I can buy the freedom
of the village and everyone in it.
So...
this whole time,
you were trying to help.
Why didn't you tell me?
- Nami, I'm your sister. Why didn't you...
- I couldn't lose you too.
Or anyone else.
So you kept that secret all these years.
And you let me hate you.
I hated you.
A shame to break up
this touching scene.
I've heard that pirates
are stashing their plunder in this area.
You two wouldn't know
anything about that, would you?
That's obviously been stolen.
By the authority of the Marines
and the World Government,
I'm going to have to confiscate it.
- No, you can't do that. It's mine!
- A hundred million Berry?
And where would you get that much money?
How did you know it was a hundred...
Arlong put you up to this, didn't he?
I... I don't know what you mean.
- No!
- Watch yourself.
Or we will take you into custody as well.
No!
You can't do this.
You can't do this!
No!
Nami, wait.
Wait. Nami, stop! Wait. Wait!
- Nami.
- Let me go! Let me go! They can't do this!
- There's nothing you can do!
- Arlong will kill the entire village!
Nami, wait!
My brothers!
We all know the truth of this world.
Fishmen are
the rightful rulers of the seas.
And the humans know it too.
They fear our power,
so they bound us with chains.
They loathe our presence,
so they banned us from their cities.
But we broke those chains, huh?
Built our own cities.
Now the time has come to restore
the natural order of this world.
Yeah!
No.
Please!
For centuries, humans have used us,
kept us down.
And our so-called leaders,
they allowed it.
Banners of unity and peace
they so lovingly wave
are, in truth,
flags of surrender, willing defeat.
I don't know about you,
but I ain't surrendering.
Kill them all!
Yeah!
We are the embodiment
of fishman superiority!
And with the Grand Line map,
we will reclaim our birthright.
Our righteous rage
will burn through Coco Village
to the ends of the East Blue,
and as we move
to the Grand Line and beyond,
we will teach each and every human
their rightful place,
beneath us.
Yeah!
Beneath us!
Beneath us! Yeah!
Yeah!
Arlong.
Arlong!
Ah!
I told you to get the hell out of here.
You did.
Then leave.
You don't know
anything about what's going on here.
I don't.
Luffy.
Help me.
Of course I will.
Of course I will!
Let's go.
Right.
What's that?
They're attacking the village.