This is a world like no other,
one brimming with mystery
and teeming with danger,
filled with hundreds of islands
strewn across vast seas.
And throughout these seas are those
who live according to their own rules,
who seek a life of freedom and adventure.
This is a world of pirates!
Piracy is a scourge upon this world.
For too long, villains and miscreants
have sown havoc across our seas.
But the Marines,
on behalf of your World Government,
strive to keep you safe and protected.
And today we've made a great stride
in that effort.
Gold Roger,
the so-called King of the Pirates,
has been captured.
His reign of terror ends this day.
Peace shall be restored.
Let this be a message to break the spirit
of anyone foolish enough
to follow in his footsteps.
Gold Roger,
you have been sentenced to death
for the crimes of piracy,
thievery,
and conspiracy
against the World Government.
- Do you have any last words?
- Yeah.
Would you take these off?
Starting to itch.
I warned you.
You brought this upon yourself.
That I did, Vice-Admiral.
Now I'm bringing it to one and all.
By the authority
of the World Government...
I declare your life
forfeit...
Pirate King,
where is your treasure?
Tell us where you hid it!
You want to know where my treasure is?
I'll tell you.
Wealth.
Fame.
Power.
I found everything
this world has to offer.
Free yourselves.
Take to the seas!
My treasure is yours to find.
Gold Roger's final words
changed the world forever.
A new age was born,
the Great Pirate Era,
setting off a race across the seas
to find the Pirate King's hidden treasure,
the One Piece.
Ever since I was a kid,
Shanks would tell me stories
about pirates and their adventures.
So, yeah, the sea's been calling.
Well, not exactly calling,
because I pretty much can't swim,
but you get the idea.
I'm setting out to follow my dream,
to find the One Piece
and become King of the Pirates!
All I need is a loyal crew.
I think about ten men should do.
Well, ten men and a bird.
It's not gonna be easy.
The ocean is... is pretty big
and kind of dangerous.
So what do you say?
Are you with me?
Mutiny.
Oy.
Oh man.
It's my first day.
Load your cannons!
Fire!
Take everything!
But leave the crew to me.
Let's show 'em
what true terror looks like.
Where is the pirate hunter Roronoa Zoro?
Don't deny he was on your ship.
He booked passage to Sixis Island.
After that, I don't know.
Liar! I know Zoro must be after me.
Who else is worthy of his pursuit?
He had a list
of pirates and their bounties.
And of course, I was at the top.
Actually, your name wasn't on it.
No! No!
- Koby, clean up this mess.
- Coming, Captain Alvida!
Who's the most powerful pirate
on the seas?
- Alvida!
- Captain Alvida!
Yeah!
Who's there?
Hey!
Knock it off!
Sh.
Please don't kill me.
- Hey.
- Please.
Hey, hey, hey.
I'm not gonna kill you, all right?
I just need you to be quiet.
First things first.
- Do you have any food here?
- What?
I'm starving.
Alvida doesn't let me eat
until after she finishes her meal.
- Who's Alvida?
- This is her ship.
- She's captain of the Alvida Pirates.
- Oh, that's great!
- It is?
- Yeah!
'Cause I'm a pirate too.
You don't look like a pirate.
- What do they look like?
- Pirates are scum.
They're thieves and murderers.
Not the pirates I know.
Shanks. He's back!
Work fast as the breeze, men!
Captain wants this haul
to the traders by nightfall.
Before those Marine bastards
get back on our trail.
Easy with this, Roux. It's worth more
than the rest of the loot put together.
Aye, captain.
Pretend it's a leg of lamb.
You wouldn't drop that.
- Here.
- Got it, Captain.
Luffy! I was wondering when you'd pop up.
Our favorite street urchin
comes to welcome us back.
How ya been, kid?
I'm not an urchin. I'm a pirate!
I'm not joking.
I'm ready to join your crew.
The sea isn't a child's game.
It's dangerous.
The scars on my face are proof of that.
I can do it, Shanks. I swear.
You're not ready.
I am. And I'll show you!
Might want to take it easy on him,
Captain.
He's got no family to speak of.
The kid's on his own.
Better a disappointed kid now
than a dead one later.
Let's get this done.
- These men need a drink.
- Aye, Captain.
- And a bath.
- Hey, Shanks!
Put it down, Luffy.
Before you hurt yourself.
I'm not afraid of getting hurt.
And I'll prove it to you.
Luffy!
I don't get it.
Why would anyone want to be a pirate?
'Cause it's the best thing there is.
You have the... the wind in your back,
the salty sea air,
your loyal crew by your side.
You never know what's on the horizon.
It's all about being... free.
Nothing's free about Alvida's crew.
She tells me when to eat, when to sleep.
I even have to paint her toenails.
- So why don't you just leave?
- No one leaves Alvida!
She'll never let me go.
You should never let anyone
tell you what you can't do.
If I did that,
I never would've left my village
to go find the One Piece.
Gold Roger's treasure?
That's impossible.
Every pirate in the world is after that.
Why shouldn't I be the one to find it?
As soon as I'm out of here,
I'm on my way to the Grand Line.
Pirate graveyard.
There are a-hundred-foot waves
and sea beasts that'll crush your bones.
Once you enter the Grand Line,
you never return.
It sounds kind of fun.
Wait!
Is... is that...
is that one of the sea beasts?
It's just Alvida snoring.
If you want to get out of here,
it's now or never.
Lifeboats are tied
at the stern of the ship.
- Gonna need one of these.
- Head due north.
- You should hit land in a few days.
- North.
Which way is north?
What the hell is going on up there?
- What's the meaning of this?
- Alvida, I can explain.
You dare betray me to a bounty hunter?
No, that's not it at all.
And you, you're too scrawny
to be Roronoa Zoro.
I'm Monkey D. Luffy.
Never heard of you.
Well, remember the name,
'cause I'm gonna be King of the Pirates.
You must be new around here, boy,
because who is
the most powerful pirate on the seas?
- Captain Alvida!
Ah.
I'm sorry. I didn't hear you, Koby.
Who's the most powerful pirate
on the seas?
- Answer me, you sniveling runt.
- He doesn't have to.
Koby's his own man.
- Shut up.
- No. No, he's not.
He's mine, and he'll always be mine.
That's not what he told me.
He said that you were mean.
And cruel.
And that you're as dumb as a sea cow.
No, Captain Alvida! I didn't!
Whoo!
Ay!
What kind of a monster are you?
The stretchy kind.
Yah!
You! This is all your fault!
Ah!
That's enough.
Gum Gum...
Pistol!
Anyone else got a problem with Koby?
No, sir.
Come on.
We're gonna need a boat
and enough food for a few days.
- Me?
- Yeah!
You're coming with me, right?
You can come out.
People often visit shrines
to light candles for those they've lost.
Who are yours for?
This one is for someone
I knew a long time ago.
And the other?
You've been following me
for three days.
- What do you want?
- You may call me Mr. 7.
I represent an organization
known as Baroque Works.
We are interested
in your unique set of skills,
pirate hunter Roronoa Zoro.
What are you? Some band of assassins?
We are much, much more.
You should know it's a high honor
to be asked to join our ranks.
Kind of got my own thing going on.
Membership would make you
even more invincible, more feared.
Does it come with a free face tattoo?
My favorite is Number 1.
To turn down Baroque Works
is to forfeit your life.
If they were that serious,
they should've sent
someone better than Number 7.
Ah!
That look on Alvida's face.
I've never seen anyone
stand up to her before.
- Shouldn't have messed with you.
- How did you stretch like that?
It's kind of a long story.
At least you didn't get your eye.
I was aiming for it, but I missed.
Ow.
- I thought you said you were tough.
- I am!
Don't stitch it too good.
I want everyone to see my scar.
Scars don't make the man, Luffy.
It's the lesson behind the scar,
and you didn't earn this one.
Then let me earn it.
I'll be the best pirate ever.
Look, I've been practicing what my face
is gonna look like on my wanted poster.
I've no doubt your mug
will be on a wanted poster one day.
But you're not ready.
My ship already has an anchor.
I'm not an anchor.
Stupid Shanks.
Stupid treasure.
There you go, Captain.
Bring us your best whiskey.
I'm afraid we're out.
That'd be our fault, friend.
We've, uh, been doing some celebrating.
We've drunk the place dry, but...
perhaps this will make up for it.
What can we do with one bottle?
Generally, you drink it.
Now there's glass everywhere.
Mmm.
Makino, got a mop?
Mm-hmm.
Since you like cleaning so much.
Come on, men.
Let's find a real bar.
- He got you good, huh, Cap'n?
- "You got a mop?"
Why are you laughing?
How could you let him
insult you like that?
All he did was spill a drink on me.
But you should've fought back!
Why didn't you kick his ass?
Not everything
can be solved with violence.
A man needs to be strong,
but he also needs to be good.
You're not a real man.
You're nothing but a coward.
You see?
I told you, you weren't ready.
Wait.
Luffy!
What have you done?
You ate a Devil Fruit?
I didn't know any better.
But mine was a Gum Gum Fruit.
It turned my body into rubber.
Eee.
Huh?
So now what?
- We have to be going somewhere, right?
- We are going somewhere.
Next stop,
to the Grand Line!
Do you know how to get there?
Hmm.
You can't navigate.
You don't even have a map!
Good point.
We should probably pick one up.
Maybe I've made a mistake.
I never should've left Alvida.
Koby, if you could do
anything in the world right now,
what would it be?
I guess there is one thing, but...
it's dumb.
- What was that for?
- You being dumb.
Now spit it out.
I've kind of...
I've always wanted to be...
a Marine.
Ah.
Ever since I was a kid,
I wanted to protect people
that can't protect themselves.
I told you it was dumb.
If that's what you want,
I think you should do it.
I'll help you out.
You don't even know me.
We shared a meal, Koby.
And if being a Marine is your dream...
that's good enough for me.
Okay.
So you plot a course
to the next Marine base.
I get my map,
and you can join up. Yeah.
All right.
Well, I'm gonna take that nap now.
You can't just waltz into a Marine base
and ask for a map to the Grand Line!
Don't worry.
I'm stealthy.
Yeah. Super stealthy.
There's someone in there.
Let's get closer.
Help me!
Water...
Oh, you're in luck, sweetheart.
We're all the help you'll need.
My crew was attacked by pirates.
I... I barely managed to make it out alive.
Pirates, you say?
I hear they're a terrible lot.
The worst sort. Good thing
we found you instead of them.
What you got there? Something to share?
No. Please, no,
it's... it's all I have. Please.
It's a fair trade for saving your life.
Hey, what gives?
Sorry, boys. Thanks for the rescue.
Hut. Hut. Hut. Hut. Hut.
I didn't know
there were so many pirates!
There are way worse pirates
on the Grand Line.
It's terrible.
Yeah.
Yeah. I know, right?
Where's my face?
Well, only one way
I'm gonna get inside that base.
And it's not on an empty stomach.
Come on.
We already have our food.
No, more is better. More is better.
You gotta feed the brain.
All right, so...
I can't get inside the base
through the gate,
but maybe... maybe...
maybe what if I get inside flying?
I can grab onto a bird or something.
That's a terrible idea.
Keep your voice down.
A bottle for me, and one for my friend.
He's had a rough day.
Hi.
Can I buy you a drink?
Too tall.
You like rum?
Yeah, sure.
As much as the next guy.
I'm not asking the next guy.
- What's this?
- Rice balls. For you.
- You made them yourself?
- Mm-hmm.
- What's the brown stuff?
- Chocolate. Makes everything taste better.
Rika?
You stupid, stupid girl.
- Why don't you watch where you're going?
- Rika, apologize to our guest.
I'm... I'm so sorry.
"I'm so sorry!"
Next time, I won't be so nice.
You dropped my food.
Mmm.
Delicious.
Now you eat one.
And apologize to the girl.
Do you know who I am?
A shithead Marine with a bad haircut.
I wouldn't do that.
Oh, come on, tough guy.
Three swords?
I only need one.
Okay.
But it's gonna hurt.
Oh.
Ah.
Wow.
Good fighter.
You shouldn't draw your blade
unless you're prepared to use it.
Don't kill me, please.
My father will give you anything you want.
Who's your father?
Captain Morgan.
He's in charge of the Marine base.
Then he owes me money.
I understand you sent
four of my Marines to the infirmary.
Without drawing a blade, I might add.
Impressive.
I didn't want to make a mess.
Roronoa Zoro.
The Demon.
Most feared pirate hunter
in the East Blue.
Hmm. I'd say
you live up to your reputation.
If it's all the same,
I'll just take my money and go.
You'll collect your bounty,
but the penalty for assaulting a Marine
is seven days strung up in the yard.
No food or water.
You can try to arrest me,
but your brat'll be the first one I kill.
Hey! He can't speak to me that way!
I like you.
Oh, we should be working
for the same team.
You'd make a hell of a Marine.
Hmm.
Kind of got my own thing going on.
Doesn't leave much time
for playing dress-up.
It's a shame
to lose a man of your talents,
since you won't be able
to collect a bounty at any Marine base
once I get the word out.
So what's it gonna be?
A new career?
Or the yard?
Seven days?
I could catch up on my sleep.
I can't stop thinking about that fight.
That guy was amazing.
And what's with the third sword?
I mean, where does it even go?
No.
He had to protect that little girl
from the Marines,
who were supposed to be protecting her.
It doesn't make any sense.
If there are good pirates
and bad pirates, then
there are gonna be good Marines
and bad Marines too.
You'll be one of the good ones.
Maybe Alvida was right.
I don't know anything about the world.
But you were her prisoner.
Yeah, but I knew who I was.
Now I have no idea.
Hey, Koby.
Koby!
I need to get into the base
and find that map,
and I could use some help.
You want me to help you
steal from the Marines?
No. Of course not.
How about you help me
get the boat ready?
You can handle that, right?
I guess so.
What are you gonna do?
I'm working on that.
Beautiful morning, isn't it?
A bit hot for my taste though.
The great Demon.
More like a misbehaving puppy
tied up in the backyard.
What do you say, puppy?
Do you want to do a trick for me?
Sit up and beg.
Hmm?
Hoo!
Put it down!
Ooh.
What's so special
about this old thing? Hmm?
Enjoy these seven days,
'cause when I get down from here,
you'll be the one begging.
When you get down?
You think my father's gonna let you go?
You are going to die in this yard.
Hut. Hut. Hut. Hut. Hut.
Hut. Hut. Hut. Hut. Hut. Hut!
Hey.
About face!
Oh, hey. You're the guy from the bar.
- Get lost.
- I am lost.
I'm trying to get inside the base.
Hey, I saw the way you fight.
How did they even arrest you?
They didn't.
I gave myself up.
Interesting choice.
I'm sure you had your reasons.
You don't know anything about me.
I know that you protected that little girl
from those Marines last night.
You're a good guy.
I'm Roronoa Zoro, the pirate hunter.
Well, I'm Monkey D. Luffy,
and I will be the King of the Pirates.
And I think you should join my crew.
What makes you think
I'd wanna play pirates with you?
You're a great fighter.
I'd say that together,
we'd make a pretty good team.
I kill your kind for a living.
Pirate... hunter.
You keep saying that,
but is that all you are?
Is that all you want?
I made a promise to someone
a long time ago...
to become the world's greatest swordsman.
Impressive.
You can untie me,
but I'm still not gonna join your crew.
Okay.
I mean it.
I don't owe you anything.
I just think it's a waste of time
for you to be hanging out here
when there's something you want out there.
Good luck on the sword thing.
Hey, can you close this behind me?
Thanks!
Hey!
You're not supposed to be in here.
Captain Morgan sent me
to find a map of The Grand Line
ahead of his security briefing
this afternoon.
Why would he do that?
All maps pertaining to The Grand Line
are kept under lock and key
in his private office.
I'm just following orders. But if you want
to question Axe-Hand Morgan, be my guest.
Hey, we don't have any maps
to The Grand Line down here, do we?
Nah, we didn't get any.
Hey, you're that girl from the bar.
The one who stole my uniform.
This is fine.
No problem.
Whoa!
Hmm.
Whoa! Hey, hey, hey! No, don't do that.
I'm taking you into custody
for trespassing on a Marine base.
Ah.
Better take yourself into custody too,
'cause you're not a Marine.
Am too.
No, you're not.
I heard everything.
You stole that guy's uniform.
And now you're looking for my map.
Your map?
Yep. My map to The Grand Line.
It's my map,
and I'm not leaving here without it.
Suit yourself.
Hey! Hey! Get back here!
Do you have any idea what you're doing?
Looking for that Morgan guy's office.
Map's there, right?
Copy that.
That's your plan?
Just walk into Axe-Hand Morgan's office
and ask him for the map?
I may have to fight him for it.
Why do they call him Axe-Hand anyways?
You are going to get us both caught
if you keep stomping around this place.
We need a plan.
Ah!
Axe-Hand!
Are you going to kill me?
Oh no.
I've got something much worse in mind.
Captain Morgan, sir, I was just
escorting this prisoner to the brig.
He was arrested
for causing a disturbance in the square.
Yeah.
Prisoner.
I've never seen you before.
I'm a transfer from the 77th, sir.
What's your name, Private?
Nami, sir.
I put in a request
to serve under your command.
Wise choice.
I expect great things from you.
Yeah. She's the best!
I... I mean, she's the best of the worst.
I hate the Marines.
Carry on.
That was amazing. Admit it.
We do make a pretty good team.
We are not a team.
Whatever you say.
Now all we have to do is figure out
a way to get into Axe-Man's office.
Are those his keys?
Oh!
How'd you do that?
I'm a thief.
Ah.
You know, you're really good at thieving...
and a good talker too.
You should think
about joining my pirate crew.
Let's get one thing straight.
I am never joining anything with you.
I hate pirates. Hate them!
That's because you don't know me yet.
This guy really likes himself.
I'm going to find the map.
Pretend you're not here.
But I am here.
Why do you
want the map so badly anyway?
I'm gonna use it to find the One Piece
and become King of the Pirates.
- Figures.
- What?
Every idiot dreams
of finding the One Piece.
People like you believe in something
and you don't even know what it is.
Well, yeah.
Don't you?
So why did you decide to become a thief?
I didn't decide. I needed to eat.
You do what you have to, to survive.
You're right.
Nothing more important than food.
Just find the map.
What's going on here?
Pirates, sir, inside the base.
We're under attack!
What pirates?
A woman with orange hair,
dressed like a Marine.
She was trying
to steal a map to The Grand Line.
My keys! Sound the alarm.
Uh...
Do you think they know we're here?
No, I think they're after the other thief
and idiot pirate trying to steal a map.
What are the odds of that?
Kidding.
But you might want to work
a little faster.
Open up!
By the authority of the 153rd Marines!
You need to hurry.
- I can't rush this!
- Please hurry!
I have an idea.
- That's your idea?
- Yeah.
How did you do that?
Whoo! Whoo!
Aren't you that drunk from the bar?
Glad I made an impression.
The imposter, the pirate hunter,
and the prisoner.
Fancy that.
The three of you working together.
Yeah. We're a crew!
- Nope, not a crew.
- Not together.
No enemy has ever escaped my wrath.
I alone defeated the Black Cat Pirates.
I alone captured
Kuro of the Thousand Plans.
And I alone keep Shells Town safe
from the scum of the East Blue.
Yah!
Ah!
Oh.
Whoa!
Yah!
It's not only the axe.
Every part of his body's a weapon.
I'll go high. You go low.
Ah.
So that's where it goes.
Ah!
Gum Gum Whip!
Whoo!
Ah!
- Gum Gum Whip?
- Yeah!
All the great fighters
call out their finishing moves.
No, they don't.
Hate to break up this beautiful moment,
but we need to get this safe out of here.
Maybe if we find some rope or something.
Or we can do that.
- Careful with that!
- Whatever you say.
Oh, wait.
I don't work for you.
I'm sensing a little bit of tension
amongst the crew.
- Not a crew!
- I can't leave without my friend.
- Can't wait. The Marines will be here.
The Marines are here already.
You're under arrest.
What's wrong with his hair?
Yeah, I might've done that.
I won't let you make a joke of me.
I'm taking you in
and handing you over to my father.
I'll be the hero.
I might even get a medal or something.
- Koby?
- God, that hurt!
It also felt really good too.
No time to explain, but we gotta go.
This whole island is trying to kill us.
I'm not coming with you.
You sure?
Before we met,
every choice was made for me.
But now I'm gonna do what I want to do.
I'm gonna be a Marine.
I want to help people
that can't help themselves.
Next time we meet, we might be enemies.
But for now...
we're friends.
This is Garp.
Pirates, you say?
Raiding our base in Shells Town.
What did they take?
Weapons? Gold?
Change of plan.
We're going to Shells Town.
Got a lead on Baroque Works?
We've been chasing those shadows
a long time. This is different.
A map to the Grand Line has been stolen...
by a pirate in a straw hat.
They were pirates, Captain,
just like us.
And they got the map.
And you didn't stop them.
I couldn't. I mean,
there were three of them.
They must've been planning this
for months.
Well, that's my map.
And I'm gonna get it back.
No matter who I have to kill.
This is my first pirate score.
From now on,
it's all gonna be smooth sailing.
This crew can handle anything.
We've been making enemies
everywhere we go.
Nothing can stop me
from taking the East Blue.
We've been captured. We need a plan.
Ah! Ah!
That went pretty well.
Arlong will kill
the entire village!
- Nami made her choice.
- Ah!
We've got
each other's backs... always.
So these are the Straw Hat Pirates.